{
  "decks": [{
    "name": "Elementary Math",
    "flashcards": [
      {
        "front": "1+1",
        "back": "2"
      },{
        "front": "2+2",
        "back": "4"
      },{
        "front": "3+3",
        "back": "6"
      },{
        "front": "4+4",
        "back": "8"
      },{
        "front": "5+5",
        "back": "10"
      }
    ]
  }, {
    "name": "Spanish",
    "flashcards": [
      {
        "front": "House",
        "back": "Casa"
      },{
        "front": "Pet",
        "back": "Mascota"
      },{
        "front": "Hello",
        "back": "Hola"
      },{
        "front": "Goodbye",
        "back": "Adios"
      },{
        "front": "Thank You",
        "back": "Gracias"
      },{
        "front": "Sorry",
        "back": "Lo Siento"
      }
    ]
  }]
}